만화방이 계속
붐비다니 놀랍지 않아?
It's amazing
people keep coming
to comic book stores
다운 받아서
볼 수 있을 텐데
instead of just downloading
comics digitally.
그게 최선일 거야
It's probably for the best.
유일하게 외출하는 날이잖아
For a lot of these guys,
the weekly trip here
엄마한테 지하실에
내려갈 기회도 줘야지
is the only chance
their mom has to go down
이불 빨래 해줘야 되니까
to the basement
and change their sheets.
그러고 보니 오늘
시트 바꾸는 날이야
Oh, that reminds me,
I get fresh sheets tonight. Yay.
어때?
Well?
만화방에 오는 것도
꽤 근사하지?
What do you think
of New Comic Book Night?
Magic, huh?
쉘든, 실망이야
Sheldon, I'm disappointed.
너처럼 똑똑한 남자는
As a brilliant man,
악습이 있을 법한지
you're entitled to a vice.
아편굴에 들락거리거나
I could understand
frequenting an opium den
재미삼아 다른 인간을
사냥할 줄 알았어
or hunting your fellow man
for sport.
겨우 만화방이라니 허접하네
But this? Lame-o.
만화는 순차적 미술에
스토리텔링 기법을 적용하지
Well, A) Comic books
employ storytelling
through sequential art,
17,000년 전 라스코동굴
벽화부터 전해 내려온 거야
an medium that dates back
17,000 years
to the cave paintings
of Lascaux,
그리고 넌 하프를 연주하잖아
and B) You play the harp.
그건 멋있다고 생각해?
Like that's cool.
특별히 찾으시는 거 있나요?
Can I help you
find anything?
여자 가슴이 부유 장치로
사용되지 않는 내용이면 좋겠어요
A comic that depicts
a woman whose bosom
can't be used
as a flotation device.
여기 오는 대부분 남자들은
빵빵한 가슴을 좋아해서요
Sorry. Most of the guys
who come in here
like big boobs.
가끔 여자보다 가슴이
큰 녀석들도 있죠
Couple of them
have big boobs.
Warlords of Ka'a
확장팩이 나왔어
Hey, look, the new
Warlords of Ka'a
expansion pack is out.
벌써?
A new one?
Unbelievable.
저급 몬스터나 만들어서
They just keep making up
more cheesy monsters,
카드에 찍어내고
$25을 받다니
slapping them on cards and
selling them at 25 bucks a pop.
경험이 없는 남자들을
노린 비밀 세금같아
It's like a secret tax
on guys who can't get laid.
너무 대충하고 있어
They're not even trying.
사탄의 동물 팩에 나온
지옥 코끼리 기억나?
Remember the Satanimals pack
with the Hellephant?
말도 안돼
Why, absurd.
나쁜 짓을 해서
지옥에 떨어진 코끼리인가?
What was he, a bad elephant
who died and went to hell?
아무리 나쁜 코끼리라도
지옥살이는 너무하잖아
What could
an elephant
possibly do that would cause him
eternal damnation?
와일드 웨스트와 마녀들?
"Wild West and Witches"?
이딴 거에
아무도 관심 없다고
What kind of loser cares
about a showdown
빌리 더 키드랑
북쪽 백마법사의 결투라니
between Billy the Kid and
the White Wizard of the North?
찌질하다
A total loser.
6연발 권총을 든 놈이 이기겠지
Obviously,
a guy with a six-shooter
상대는 마술 지팡이를
휘두르는 노인네잖아
beats an old man
with a magic wand.
잠깐
Well, h-hold on.
빌리가 쓴 모자에
'혼란의 헬멧' 주문을 건다면?
Uh, what if the wizard casts
a Helmet of Confusion spell
on Billy the Kid's cowboy hat?
뭐라는 거야
What? Please!
빌리 더 키드잖아
This is Billy the Kid
we're talking about.
마법사가 입을 떼기도 전에
I mean, the wizard
would get shot between the eyes
총알이 이마를
뚫고 지나갈 거야
before he could ever
get out the words,
"이 신비로운 땅에
빌리가 웬일이지?"
"What the hell
is Billy the Kid doing
in the mystic realm of Ka'a?"
레너드
Leonard...
쉘든이 데리고 온
에이미는 누구야?
What's the deal
with Sheldon's friend Amy?
여자친구야?
Are they a couple?
쉘든만큼 괴짜인 친구지
Couple of weirdos. Why?
에이미한테 관심 있어?
You interested in Amy?
불알이 쪼그라들게 하거나
영혼을 뺏아갈 것처럼
Well, I mean,
she didn't look through me
with soul-sucking,
ball-shriveling
증오와 멸시의 눈빛으로
쳐다보지는 않았잖아
hatred and contempt.
난 그런 여자가 좋더라
I like that in a woman.
데이트 신청하고 싶은데
쉘든 허락 좀 받아줘
Could you run it by Sheldon
if I could ask her out?
그러지 뭐
Sure. I guess.
스튜어트,
문제 좀 해결해줘
Stuart, settle an
argument for us.
누가 이길까?
Who would win,
빌리 더 키드 아니면
백마법사?
Billy the Kid
or the White Wizard?
답을 알려주면
If I tell you that,
$24.95라는 저렴한 가격에
얻을 수 있는 재미가 없어져
I'm robbing you of the hours
of fun you could have
for the magical, rootin'-tootin'
low price of $24.95.
하나 살게
I'll take one.
두 개 부탁해
Mm... make it two.
너네랑 내 자신이 싫어진다,
세 개 갖다 줘
I hate all of you and myself.
Three.
주문 들어간다
I'll ring it up.
너무 쉽게 걸려드네
Like shooting nerds in a barrel.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x10
The Flaming Spittoon Acquisition
Original Air Date on November 17, 2011
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
얘기 좀 할까?
Hey, can I talk to
you about something?
좀 꺼려지긴 하네
It's a little
awkward.
무슨 얘기 하려는지 알아
I know what this is about.
연구에 아무런 진전이 없어서
Given the professional
standstill you're at,
적절한 시기인지 고민 중이잖아
you're wondering
if this is the appropriate time
연구를 포기하고
가르치는 일에 집중할지
to abandon your research
and focus on teaching.
적절해
Yes.
또 제안을 하자면
And if I may suggest,
전공을 바꾸는 건 어때
consider changing disciplines.
인문학으로,
역사학도 괜찮고
Yeah, to the humanities--
perhaps history.
역사를 가르치는 것의 장점은
One of the advantages
of teaching history
꾸며낼 필요가 없다는 거야
is that you don't have
to create things.
지난 일을 외우고
되풀이하면 돼
You know, you just
have to remember
stuff that happened
and then parrot it back.
재밌을 거야
You could have fun with that.
그 얘기가 아니잖아
Yeah, that's not it.
스튜어트가
에이미한테 관심 있대
Stuart's kind of
interested in Amy.
물론 그렇겠지
에이미는 흥미로운 대상이야
Oh, of course he is.
She's very interesting.
14살 때는 발가락 사이의
갈퀴를 혼자 끊은 거 알아?
Did you know,
when she was 14,
she severed the webbing
between her own toes?
아니
No.
데이트 신청해도
너랑 괜찮은 건지 물어보래
He wanted me to find out
if you'd have a problem
with him asking her out.
어떻게 반응해야
하는지 모르겠다
I'm not sure how to respond,
Leonard.
에이미는 내 소유가 아냐
I don't own Amy.
사람을 소유할 수 없지
Can't own a person.
언제부터 안 그랬을까?
At least not since...
1863년
1863.
링컨 대통령이
누구를 해방시켰지?
President Lincoln freed the...
답은 노예잖아
Slaves!
Come on, Leonard,
역사를 가르치려면
if you're going
to teach history,
이런 건 기본으로 알아야해
these are the kind of facts
you'll have to know.
됐어
You know what?
Never mind.
그냥 네가 허락했다고 말할게
I'm going to tell him
it's okay to ask her out.
물어볼 것도 없지
The question is moot.
스튜어트는 가능성이 없어
There is no way that Stuart,
가난한 그림책
판매원일 뿐이잖아
an impoverished peddler
of picture books,
에이미는 저명한
신경생물학자야
would be at all appealing
to Amy Farrah Fowler,
a noted neurobiologist
생크림캔에서 얻은
아산화질소를 마취제로 이용해
capable of performing surgery
on her own feet
with nothing but nitrous oxide
발 수술까지 진행했다고
from cans of whipped cream
as anesthesia.
알았어
All right,
but for the record,
나중에 안 물어봤다는
소리나 하지 마
I checked in with you
to see how you'd feel about it.
그래, 분명히 기억할게
Fine.
The record shall so reflect.
이제 더 큰 문제를 다뤄보자
Now, getting back
to the problem at hand,
가망 없는 실험 물리학자를
어떻게 할 것인가
what to do with a washed-up
experimental physicist...
난 가망이 없지 않아
I am not washed-up.
이런, 레너드
Oh, Leonard.
많은 사람들은 널 사랑하고
돕고 싶어하는데
Lots of people love you
and want to help you,
우선 너부터
문제를 인식해야돼
but they can't
until you admit the problem.
드디어 한 병 비웠다
Well, ladies,
we killed the bottle.
난 반 잔 마셨어
I had half a glass.
난 하나도 안 마셨고
I didn't have any.
날 이상하게 보지 마
Okay, don't judge me.
이제 뭐할까?
So, what do you want to do--
영화 보거나 춤을 추거나
아니면 그냥 앉아서 쉴까?
go to the movies, go dancing,
lay down for a little bit?
트래블 트위스터 게임은 어때?
Or we play... Travel Twister.
정말?
트위스터를?
Amy, really? Twister?
이 게임을 하면서
난 즐거웠던 적이 많아
Excuse me.
I've passed many
an enjoyable evening
playing this game.
다른 사람들이랑 놀면
더 재밌을 거야
And I'm sure it's
a lot more exciting
when you play with other people.
팀을 나누자,
입을래 벗을래?
What do you say, bestie?
We can do shirts and skins.
난 옷 입는 팀이다,
찜!
I'm shirts. Called it.
난 작아서
못 하는 게 많아
I'm too small
for Twister.
트위스터,
롤러코스터 타기
And roller coasters.
발바닥이 땅에 닿게 앉기
And sitting with my
feet on the floor.
엄마, 출산 전
흡연 좋으셨겠어요
Hope you enjoyed the
prenatal cigarettes, Mom.
우리 엄마는
마리화나를 했는데
Hey, you know, my mom smoked pot
난 아무렇지도 않아
when she was pregnant with me,
and I turned out just fine.
앗, 복숭아 슈납스다
*독한 술의 일종
Hey, look, I have
peach schnapps.
Thank God.
얘들아, 큰일 났어
Guys, something happened.
무슨 일이야?
What's wrong?
누가 날 좋아하나봐
I think a boy
likes me.
안녕, 난 스튜어트야
"Hi. It's Stuart.
만화방에서 본 적 있지?
"We met at the
comic book store.
시간 날 때
커피 마시러 갈래?
"I was wondering
if you'd like
"to get coffee sometime.
거절해도 괜찮아
"It's okay
if you say no.
제대로 자극 받아서
항우울제를 먹기 시작하겠지
"It might be the kick
in the pants I need
to start taking Zoloft."
에이미,
여우 같은 여자였네
Amy, little vixen.
울이랑 폴리에스터를 껴입고도
매력을 발산하는구나
Just working it under all those
layers of wool and polyester.
어떻게 할 거야?
What are you going to do?
남자친구 있는 거 모르나?
Doesn't he know
you have a boyfriend?
남자친구 없어
Oh, she doesn't
have a boyfriend;
쉘든이 있는 거지
she has a Sheldon.
스튜어트 어때?
So do you
like Stuart?
잘 모르겠어
I don't know.
친절하고
He's nice.
재밌고
He's funny.
갑상선 호르몬이 과다해서
얼굴에 핏기가 없어 보여
He has the sallow,
drawn countenance
associated with an overactive
thyroid gland.
그건 좀 멋지다
That's kind of hot.
그래, 쉘든도 좋은데
Okay, look, sweetie,
we all love Sheldon,
벌써 1년이나 지났어
but you've been with him
over a year now.
더 이상 진전이 없다면
If it's not going anywhere,
둘러보는 것도 나쁘지 않지
what does it hurt
to look around?
나랑 하워드처럼
약혼한 사이도 아니니까 뭐
Well, yeah, I guess
they're not engaged
like me and Howie.
도움이 될지 모르지만
Yeah, for what it's worth,
약혼했어도 상관 없어
engaged people
can look around, too.
옵션은 많다고
Lot of options out there.
스튜어트 어딨어요?
Where's Stuart?
나갔어요
Out.
누구시죠?
Who are you?
데일이라고 해요
I'm Dale.
가게를 저한테 맡겼어요
He left me in charge.
정말요?
Really?
네
Yeah.
저도 이유를 모르겠어요
I don't get it, either.
'와일드 웨스트와 마녀'
확장팩 반품하려고 왔어요
I want to return
this "Wild West and Witches"
Ka'a expansion pack.
반품은 제 담당이 아니에요
Sorry. I don't do returns.
너무 어려워요
They're hard.
그래요
Sure, sure.
스튜어트는 언제 와요?
Uh, when will
Stuart be back?
커피 마시러 갔어요
I don't know.
He went out for coffee.
여자랑
With a girl.
내가 잘못 생각했네
Oh, I guess I was wrong.
괜찮아?
You okay?
괜찮냐고?
Am I okay?
내 인생 궤도는
노벨상을 향하고 있어
Leonard,
I'm on a lifelong trajectory
내 이름을 딴 도시도
많이 생길 거야
that includes a Nobel Prize
and cities named after me,
내 사랑니는 잘 자라서
뽑을 필요가 없고
all four
wisdom teeth
fit comfortably in my mouth
without need of extraction,
내 배변 활동은 독일 열차처럼
시간을 칼같이 지키고 있어
and my bowel movements run
like a German train schedule.
내가 괜찮냐고?
Am I okay?
저도 괜찮아요
I'm okay, too!
와일드 빌 위치콕
Wild Bill Witchcock.
코만치족
A tribe of Abra-Comanches.
불타는 침통
Flaming Spittoon.
참고로
And for the record,
너네는 카우보이로서
자세가 안 돼 있어
I'm very disappointed
in you cowpokes.
'와일드 웨스트와 마녀'를
처음으로 하는데
We're playing
our inaugural round
of "Wild West and Witches,"
나만 제대로 차려 입었잖아
and I'm the only one
who bothered
to dress for the occasion.
퉤
Patooie.
우리는 카우보이 모자
안 쓸 거야
We're not wearing
cowboy hats, Sheldon.
바보 같아 보여
It looks ridiculous.
내 카우보이 부츠도
바보 같아?
And I suppose my boots and spurs
are ridiculous, too?
- 응
- 좀 많이 그래
- Yeah. - Very. - Incredibly so.
사탄의 동물 팩을 사고
마왕 고양이 분장을 한 건?
Did it look ridiculous
when we got the Satanimals pack
and I dressed up
as a Beelzebobcat?
그것도 그래
- Yeah. - Very. - Incredibly so.
그래, 그냥 하자
All right, fine.
Let's just play.
너무 심하게 대하지 말자
We should go easy on him.
에이미가 스튜어트랑
데이트 중이야
Amy's out with Stuart tonight.
그러니까
Wait a minute.
쉘든 특유의 우월감과 금욕이
여자를 잡기에 부족하단 말야?
Are you telling me
that Sheldon's patented blend
of condescension and no sex
isn't enough
to hold on to a woman?
Cluck, cluck, cluck.
퀼트 만드는
아줌마들의 모임이냐?
What are we,
ladies at a quilting bee?
신비로운 마을에서 남자답게
판타지 카드게임을 하는 중이잖아
Or are we men
playing a fantasy card game
set in a magical frontier town?
미안
Sorry.
오싹한 천막
Creepy Tepee.
못생긴 애니
Annie Ogly.
호커스 포커스
포카혼타스
Hocus Pocus Pocahontas.
스튜어트랑 에이미에
집착하는 건 너네들이야
And may I point out
it is the three of you
who are obsessed with
Stuart and Amy, not me.
누가 바보 같은지
생각 좀 하라고
I think you need
to ask yourselves
who's really being
ridiculous here.
바로 너야
- It's you. - You are. - Totally you.
얘들아, 이것 좀 봐
Hey, guys, check it out.
한정판 확장팩이 나왔어
The deluxe limited edition
"Wild West and Witches"
사인 돼 있는
특별 케이스에 들어 있어
expansion pack in the signed
and numbered collector's tin.
이럴 수가
Come on, no!
일반팩을 방금 샀잖아
We just bought the regular pack.
보안관 배지다
Ooh, a sheriff's badge.
마술봉으로 변신!
Yeah, it's also a wand.
홀로그램까지?
멋지다
With a hologram? Nice!
보고 있어?
Hey, do you see this?
난 매트릭스 안에서
모든 걸 보고 있지
I'm in the matrix, Leonard;
I see everything.
뭐하는 거야
You got to be
kidding me.
스튜어트랑
페북 친구 먹었네?
You friended Stuart
on Facebook?
페이스북
싫어하는 거 아니였어?
I thought you didn't
like Facebook anymore.
어리석은 것
Don't be silly.
난 인간 교류를 대체할만한
모든 것의 팬이라고
I'm a fan of anything that tries
to replace actual human contact.
Please.
데이트가 어땠는지
확인하려는 거잖아
You're looking at Facebook
to find out how their date went.
장난해?
Really?
내가 신경 쓸 거 같아?
You think I care if a man, what,
'아리따운 여인이랑
호박 라떼를 마셨다'
"shared a pumpkin latte
with a dynamite lady"?
뻥 치시네
You're so full of it.
맘대로 생각해라
You are free to believe
whatever you like.
라지랑 친구 끊기
And unfriend
Rajesh Koothrappali.
진짜 끊었어?
You unfriended me? Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
재미난 업데이트는
다 놓치겠네
Now he's gonna miss all
those great updates like,
"이제서야 포푸리를
직접 만들어보다니"
"I can't believe
I waited this long
to make my own potpourri""
쉘든, 그냥 에이미를
좋아한다고 인정하고
Sheldon, why don't you
just acknowledge
that you have feelings for Amy
다른 남자랑 지내지
말라고 하면 되잖아
and you don't want her
going out with other men?
레너드랑 친구 끊기
And unfriend
Leonard Hofstadter.
엄청난 생각이 났어
Here's a radical thought.
전통적인 방식으로
스튜어트랑 대결을 하는 거야
Go old-school,
challenge Stuart to a fight.
여자들이 그만큼
좋아하는 것도 없어
I mean, nothing makes
the ladies hotter
빼빼 마른 남자 둘이서
파닥거리는 모습 말이야
than two skinny white guys
swatting at each other
with their eyes closed.
하워드와 친구 끊기
And unfriend Howard Wolowitz.
모두 끊겼네
That's all of us.
- 노트북 좀 써도 돼?
- 왜?
- Can I use the laptop?
- Why?
특별 한정판 사야겠어
I have to buy that
stupid collector's tin.
- 누구를 사랑한다고?
- 페니
Who do we love?
Penny.
쉘든, 안녕
Hello, Sheldon.
어서 와
Come on in.
고마워
Thank you.
무슨 일이야?
What's up?
데이트 신청하러 왔어
I came to ask if you would like
to go on a date with me.
뭐?
I'm sorry, what?
데이트
A date.
너랑 나
You and me.
식사하고
춤 추는 거야
Dining, dancing,
권투 시합을 구경해도 되고
perhaps you'd like to
take in a prizefight.
질투 작전이구나?
God, are you trying
to make Amy jealous?
아냐
No.
왜 다들 에이미랑
스튜어트에 집착하는 거야?
Why is everyone so obsessed
with Amy and Stuart?
호박 라떼를 더 마시든
Whether or not they may be
having more pumpkin lattes
섹스를 하든 알게 뭐야
or intercourse tonight.
내 말 좀 들어봐
Okay, listen to me.
그런 작전은 효과 없어
Playing games is not
gonna help get Amy back.
에이미 마음을
되돌리려는 거 아냐
I am not trying to get her back.
궁금해서 그런데
효과 있는 방법은 뭐야?
But, out of curiosity,
what is a way?
내 경험을 말해줄게
All right, honey,
let me tell you a story.
마음에 드는 남자가 있었는데
고백한 적이 없어
There was a guy I liked,
and I never told him how I felt.
결국 다른 여자를 만나더라고
Eventually, he started
going out with someone else,
난 여태까지 후회 중이야
and I always regretted it.
무슨 말인지 알겠지?
Do you see
where I'm going with this?
알 것 같아
I believe I do.
Mm.
내가 그 남자구나
I'm the guy.
아니거든
You're not the guy.
확실해?
Are you sure?
많은 게 설명될 텐데
That would explain so much.
우리 집에
자주 놀러오고
Your constant presence
in my apartment,
내 곁에 있으려고
레너드랑 시간 낭비하잖아
that baffling dalliance
with Leonard just to be near me,
'자기야'라고 부르기도 하고
the way you call me
"sweetie" all the time.
누구나 다 그렇게 불러
I call everyone "sweetie."
이런 바람둥이
You tramp.
남자답게 두 쪽을 차고
에이미랑 얘기해봐
Look, Sheldon,
all I'm saying is
strap on a pair
and go talk to Amy.
두 쪽을 차다니?
"Strap on a pair"?
스케이트?
Of what, skates?
확실히 넌 그 남자가 아니다
Oh, sweetie,
you are so not the guy.
지루하면 가도 돼
If you're bored,
you can go.
이해할게
I understand.
재밌는데 왜
No, I'm having a nice time.
괜히 치켜세울 거 없어
Don't patronize me.
실례하겠습니다
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
안녕, 스튜어트
Hi, Stuart.
안녕, 쉘든
Hi, Sheldon.
Pardon me... Excuse me...
쉘든, 여긴 어쩐 일이야?
Sheldon, what are
you doing here?
스튜어트 같은 놈이랑
어두운 영화관에 둬서 불쾌해
The thought of you
sitting in a darkened theater
with a character
like Stuart is repellent.
나쁜 뜻은 아냐, 스튜어트
No offense, Stuart.
알아
None taken.
불쾌하다는 건
좀 너무하긴 하다
Although "repellent" is kind
of a... kind of a strong word.
불편하게 했다면 미안해
I'm sorry this causes
you discomfort,
하지만 우리의
제한된 관계를 생각하면
but based on the currently
established parameters
불쾌한 상황에
처하건 말건 내 마음이야
of our relationship,
I can put myself
in any repellent
situation I want.
다시 말하지만...
Um, again...
스튜어트, 무례하게 굴지 마
Stuart, please.
You're being rude.
더 할 말 있어?
Anything else?
우리 관계를
다시 정의하고 싶어
I believe I would
like to alter
the paradigm
of our relationship.
듣는 중이야
I'm listening.
육체적인 활동을 포함한
모든 게 변하지 않다는 가정 하에
With the understanding
that nothing changes whatsoever,
physical or otherwise,
네가 여자친구가 아니라고
부인하는 것을 멈춰도 반대 안해
I would not object to us
no longer characterizing you
as "not my girlfriend."
흥미롭군
Interesting.
이제 좀 긍정적으로
표현해볼까
Now try it without the
quadruple negative.
너무 어렵잖아
You're being impossible.
안녕, 스튜어트
Hi, Stuart.
알았어
Fine.
에이미
Amy...
내 여자친구가 돼줄래?
will you be my girlfriend?
응
Yes.
이제 그만하자
Well, that's enough
of that.
방해해서 미안
Sorry to interrupt.
즐거운 시간 보내
You two enjoy your date.
팁 좀 남기고 갈게
Here's a dollar
for your troubles.
왕꿈틀이나 사 먹어
Get yourself
some Sour Patch Kids.
실례합니다
Excuse me... Excuse me...
Pardon me...
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
다른 남자랑 관계를
발전시킨 것 빼고는 좋았어
So, other than you
taking your relationship
to the next level with
another guy, this was nice.
바래다줘서 고마워
Yes, well, thanks for
seeing me to my door.
별 거 아냐
Oh, you're welcome.
에이미
Amy. Amy. Amy.
밖에 정리 좀 하자
Let's wrap things up out there.
잘자, 스튜어트
Um, good night, Stuart.
잘자
Good night.
알아들었지, 스튜어트?
Take the hint, Stuart.
잘자라고 했다
The lady said
"Good night."
여긴 어떻게 들어왔어?
How did you get
into my apartment?
이제 내 여자친구라고
잔소리 시작하는 거야?
Wow. Is that the kind
of nagging I can expect
now that you're my girlfriend?
이걸 준비해서 다행이다
Good thing I drew this up.
뭔데?
What's that?
연애 계약서야
I present to you
the relationship agreement.
서로의 권리와 책임을
정리한 31페이지 서류야
A binding covenant that,
in its 31 pages,
enumerates, iterates
and codifies
쉘든 리 쿠퍼는
이하 '남자친구'라 하고
the rights and responsibilities
of Sheldon Lee Cooper,
here and after known
as "the boyfriend,"
에이피 파라 파울러는
이하 '여자친구라' 부른다
and Amy Farrah Fowler, here and
after known as "the girlfriend""
너무 낭만적이다
It's so romantic.
서로에게 배상을
약속하는 건 낭만적이지
Mutual indemnification
always is.
도장 갖고 올테니
속독 좀 하고 있어
Why don't you start perusing
while I set up my notary stamp.
섹션 5 : 손 잡기
"Section 5:
Hand-holding.
손을 잡는 건
다음 경우에만 허용된다
"Hand-holding
is only allowed
"under the following
circumstances.
첫째, 상대방이 낭떠러지에서
떨어질 위험에 처해 있을 경우
"A: Either party is in danger
of falling off a cliff,
"precipice or ledge;
둘째, 노벨상 수상을
축하하는 경우
"B: Either party is deserving
of a hearty handshake
"after winning
a Nobel Prize;
셋째, 독감 주사를 맞으면서
서로에게 의지하는 경우
C: Moral support
during flu shots""
조금 제한적이네
Seems a bit
restrictive.
변호사를 부르던가
Feel free to retain a lawyer.
페니, 오른손은 빨간색이야
Penny, I said "right hand red."
들었어
Yeah, I heard you.
빨간색 짚었어
I got red.
베르나데트,
왼발을 노란색에
Bernadette, left
foot yellow.
다음에는 림보 하자
We should play limbo next.
아무도 날 이길 수 없어
No one beats me at limbo.
페니, 에이미,
베르나데트
Penny. Amy. Bernadette.
내 남자친구야
That's my boyfriend.
들어와
It's open!
손가락에 가시 박혔어
I got a splinter.
그래서 어쩌라고?
What do you want me
to do about it?
연애 계약서 섹션 4 :
'아야'에 '호오' 해 주기
Relationship agreement
Section 4: Boo-boos and Ouchies.
네가 해줘야지
You have to take care of it.
변호사를 부를 걸 그랬네
I should've gotten a lawyer.
우리 둘만 남았네
Looks like it's just us playing.
페니?
Penny?
페니, 와인 떨어졌어
Penny, we're out of wine!
운전은 네가 해
You should probably drive.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==